Fahad Bilal Saleem

Hi there! I am a Front-End Web Developer with 3+ years of experience in designing websites using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, ReactJs and now getting a grip on VUEJs and UI/UX design. I have hand on experience with ES6, HTML5, CSS3, and BootStrap. I create, update, optimize and modify websites according to the needs of my employers and customers. I had a good team and company previously and they supported me throughout my time at the company and I would love to join a successful, hard-working team to pursue a new role.



- bilalmughal030@gmail.com
- Dubai, United Arab Emirates
- linkedin.com/in/bilalmughal97
- github.com/bilalmughal1
- •• medium.com/@bilalmughal-1

- +971 50 363 1621
- fahadbilal.me
- @yourboyfahad
- stackoverflow.com/users/19581750/bilal-mughal?tab=profile
- (o) instagram.com/bilalmughal.1

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Brainz Technologies

02/2019 - 03/2022

It is an Islamabad-based IT solutions company, providing services to national and international clients. I had the privilege to work with a supportive, dedicated, and passionate team.

Frontend Developer/ Web Designer

- I was responsible for designing, creating, updating, and testing dynamic Web Pages, Blog Sites, and E-Commerce Stores using Using WordPress and Shopify.
- I learned many new things and completed my task before the given deadline.

Contact: Abdul Rehman - info@brainztechnologies.com

Teacher

Science Locus School

05/2017 - 06/2018 High School

Gujranwala, Pakistan

English/Urdu/Social Studies Teacher

- 2017 Best Teacher Award, Cherished Among Students, Likeable among Fellow Teachers.
- English/ Urdu/ Social Studies Teacher
- It was a great honor for me to teach when I was also a student and it was a blessing. I loved every moment of teaching.

Contact: Professor Muhammad Asif - +92 300 6475963

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Domotica (11/2021 - 04/2022)

 Domotica is a web and app-based home automation system. It contains an entire system dedicated to you and your home. It is controlled by a central hub that is contacted to your home Wi-Fi network and all the devices that you want to control by web app or mobile app. It is easy to control and manage, It is designed to ease the life of the user and to fulfil its main purpose "Energy

EDUCATION

Master's In Computer Science(MCS)

The Superior University Lahore

11/2020 - 04/2022

Lahore, Pakistan

Courses

 OPP. DLD. SE. AI. TOA. OS. DAA. Communication Skills

Associate Degree Program(ADP)

University Of Central Punjab

11/2018 - 08/2020

Courses C++, OPP, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT,

Communication Skills

INTERESTS

LANGUAGES

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Englishh

Urdu

Coding	Writing	Gaming	Reading
Movies	Cricket	Fitness	Music

Lahore, Pakistan